Look at my pussy.
私のマンコを見てください
I would like you to slowly close your pussy.
ゆ っくりマンコを閉じたりしたいとしてもらいたいんですけど、
Shall I turn my hands from the front?
手を前から回しましょうか
It's smooth and beautiful.
ツルツルで綺麗ですね
so?
そんなに?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Can I see it?
見ていいですか?
yes.
はい
I'll spread it out.
広げますよ
I'm watching.
見てます
I'll take it off.
外しますね
Can I have you hold my leg again?
また足を押さえてもらっていいですか?
Measure the temperature.
温度を測ります
yes.
はい
It's 36.4℃.
36.4℃です
36.4℃
It will be higher than when measured from the armpit, but
脇で測るより高めになるんですけど、
It's okay if you don't feel too much.
あまり気持ちなくて大丈夫です
Press it where it feels comfortable,
自分で気持ちいいところに押し当てて、
When you go, tell the big kids you're going.
行くときは大きな子に行くって言ってください
Please show me where you are going again.
もう一回行くとこ見せてください
yes.
はい
Let's go!
行くぜ!